Guide to the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) photographs, audiovisual, and publications, 1944-2014 MS2374
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographic material and paper records, Series 1
  - Color slides, Series 1 Subseries 4
    - Construction B-10 2, November 1987 - August 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Construction B-11, Glenmont, May 1986 - April 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Construction B-11, Glenmont Station, June 1994 - July 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Construction B-11, Glenmont Tunnels, November 1993 - October 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Construction B-12, Glenmont Yard, June 1994 - January 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Construction C-1, March 1971 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Construction C-2, March 1971 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Construction C-3, September 1971 - May 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Construction C-10 a, b, May 1978 - May 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Construction C-10 c, May 1978 - July 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Construction C-11, Mat 1978 - November 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Construction D-1, July 1973 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Construction D-2, September 1972 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Construction D-3, November 1972 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Construction D-4, March 1973 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Construction D-6, July 1973 - February 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Construction D-8, D-9, March 1974 - February 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Groundbreaking, December 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Construction A-3 2, November 1971 - July 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Construction A-3 3, July 1973 - December 1976; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Construction A-4 1, September 1970 - June 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Construction A-4 2, June 1972 - August 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Construction A-4 3, August 1974 - May 1976; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Construction A-6 1, October 1973 - March 1980; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Construction A-6 2, March 1980 - October 1981; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Construction A-9, December 1975 - December 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Construction A-10, A-11, A-12, September 1975 - December 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Construction - Cut & Cover, September 1965 - August 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Construction - General 1, March 1966 - February 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Construction - General 2, January 1969 - February 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Construction - General 3, February 1969 - November 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Construction - Occb, pyramid, stables, underpinning, July 1970 - May 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Construction A-1 1, April 1971 - April 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Construction A-1 2, April 1974 - March 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Construction A-2 1, April 1970 - March 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Construction A-2 2, March 1972 - March 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Construction A-3, March 1971 - November 1971; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Buses, Signs 1, May 1982 - June 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Bus, Telephone, March 1973 - February 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Ceremony 1, November 1977 - September 1981; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Ceremony 2, February 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Certificates, Charts 1, March 1962 - November 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Charts 2, September 1972 - June 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Charts 3, August 1987 - June 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Civic 1, March 1962 - June 1969; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Civic 2, June 1969 - March 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Bus: Lift, Marta, Neoplan, Orion, August 1974 - May 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Bus: Omnibus, Rear Lights, February 1978 - February 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Bus, Roadeo 1, July 1978 - September 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Bus, Roadeo 2, October 1985 - June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Bus, Roadeo 3, July 1987 - May 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Bus: Safety, Service Truck, Shelters, October 1972 - November 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Bus Service, Vehicle Maintenance, March 1982 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Bus: Shirley Highway Express, Shops 1, May 1971 - June 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Bus: Shops 2, June 1973 - May 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Bus General 1, May 1992 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Bus General 2, October 1979 - April 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Bus General 3, April 1991 - November 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Bus General 4, November 1999 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Bus: Georgetown, Historic, Inspection, May 1980 - October 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Bus: Interiors, Kneeling, February 1978 - August 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Bus, Landmarks 1, June 1973 - June 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Bus, New Design, April 1973 - September 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Bus, Miscellaneous, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Bus, Landmarks 2, April 1984 - August 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Buses: E&H Service, Farmer's Project, Failbox, February 1979 - August 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Bus Garage, Four Mile, July 1973 - May 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Bus Garage, Montgomery, October 1981 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Bus Garage, Northern, July 1973 - September 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Bus, PRTC Garage, September 1998 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Bus Garage, Royal Street, July 1973 - May 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Bus Garage, Prince George's, July 1973 - May 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Bus Garage, Southeast, July 1973 - May 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Bus Garage, Western, November 1974 - September 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Bus General 1, April 1970 - March 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Board 5, December 1972 - October 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Board 6, October 1978 - January 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Board, February 1967 - March 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Buses: Aerial, Articulated, Cleaning, April 1979 - October 1986; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Buses: Cold Start, October 1981 - May 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Buses: Control Center, December 1976 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Buses: Downtown, Early Graphics, June 1973 - February 1979; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Buses: Flexible, Garage Arlington, July 1973 - September 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Bus Garage, Bladensburg, July 1973 - May 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Bus Garage, Bladensburg 2, May 1987 - May 1993; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Bus Garage, Bladensburg 3, May 1993 - December 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Accidents, September 1977 - June 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Aerials, March 1962 - July 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Advertisement, March 1962 - June 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Apta Convention & Roadeo, October 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Architecture: A-File, November 1972 - April 1981; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Architecture: B-File 1, July 1971 - November 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Architecture: B-File 2, June 1973 - May 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Architecture: C-File 1, September 1970 - April 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Architecture: C-File 2, September 1970 - December 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Architecture: C-D File, April 1967 - July 1980; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Architecture: Early Art Work, April 1962 - June 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Architecture: E-File, July 1966 - January 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Architecture: F-File, March 1968 - October 1974; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Architecture: F-G File 1, September 1971 - March 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Architecture: F-G File 2, November 1967 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Trains: Prototype 2, October 1968 - November 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Trains: ROHR Scenic, Shady Grove Scenic, April 1984 - April 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Trains: Test 1, August 1976 - August 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Trains: Test 2, August 1982 - October 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Transit Systems 1, November 1992 - October 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Trains: Vandalism, October 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Vehicles, Unconventional, March 1962 - July 1973; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Uniforms, July 1973 - September 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Yard: West Falls Church, November 1985 - August 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - ADSV, March 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Trains: Control Center, May 1975 - May 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Trains: General, November 1974 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Trains: Eisenhower Ave, I-66, Landmarks, New Carrollton, September 1983 - September 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Trains: E & D Service, May 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Trains: Greenbelt, Naylor Road, April 1999 - July 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Trains: First Arrive, First in Tunnel, August 1974 - March 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Trains: Interiors 1, March 1975 - November 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Trains: Interiors 2, November 1989 - November 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Train: Operators, April 1976 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Trains: Prototype 1, May 1968 - September 1968; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Tours 3, May 1985 - December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Traffic, October 1962 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Training, May 1975 - May 1980; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Trains: Alex. S & I, Breda Cars, December 1981 - December 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Trains: Brentwood 1, February 1976 - November 1981; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Trains: Brentwood 2, October 1981 - June 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Training: Rail, Rail Safety, October 1983 - June 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Trains: Cleaning, August 1981 - March 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Trains: Disaster Drill, November 1982 - October 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Foreign Cities: Moscow, Oslo, January 1962 - December 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Cities: Stockholm, Sao Paulo, Rotterdam, Rome, Rio de Janiero, Paris, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Cities: Sweden, Toronto, Tokyo, Vienna, December 1961 - September 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Cities: Mexico City, June 1971; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Cities: Seattle, Washington D.C., March 1963 - October 1972; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Cities: Montreal, August 1966 - December 1968; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Cities: Buenos Aires, Budapest, Brussels, Berlin, Barcelona, Athens, September 1961 - April 1966; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 78B, Folder 7)
    - Stations: Shady Grove, Shaw-Howard U, Silver Spring 1, January 1978 - May 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Stations: Van Dorn, Van Ness, Vienna, Virginia-Square GMU, November 1979 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Stations: Waterfront, West Falls Church, West Hyattsville, November 1985 - June 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Stations: Wheaton 1, August 1990 - May 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Stations: White Flint, Woodley Park - Zoo, December 1981 - April 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Street Cars, Strikers, Test and Evaluation Center, March 1970 - September 1975; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Tours 1, April 1972 - May 1977; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Tours 2, May 1977 - May 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Station: Rhode Island Ave 2, January 1978 - August 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Stations: Rockville, Rosslyn, May 1977 - September 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Station: Silver Spring 2, February 1983 - December 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Station: Silver Spring 3, January 1989 - June 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Station: Smithsonian 1, July 1977 - June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Station: Smithsonian 2, July 1991 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Station: Southern Avenue, May 2001 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Stations: Stadium Armory, Suitland, Takoma, Tenleytown, Twinbrook, May 1977 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Stations: U-Street, Union Station, Van Dorn, March 1976 - August 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Stations: Minnesota Avenue, Mount Vernon Square - UDC, May 1978 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Stations: National Airports 1, April 1977 - March 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Stations: National Airports 2, October 1987 - December 1995; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Stations: National Airports 3, December 1995 - May 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Stations: National Airports 4, September 1996 - November 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Stations: Navy Yard, Naylor Road, December 1991 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Stations: New Carrollton 1, October 1978 - August 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Stations: New Carrollton 2, February 1995 - May 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Stations: Pentagon, Pentagon City, Potomac Avenue, Prince George's Plaza, May 1977 - April 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Stations: Rhode Island Avenue 1, January 1975 - January 1978; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Station: Gallery Place 1, May 1975 - May 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Station: Gallery Place 2, May 1996 - March 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Station: Gallery Place 3, November 1997 - April 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Stations: Georgia Ave - Petworth, Glenmont, Greenbelt, November 1993 - June 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Stations: Judiciary Square, King Street, September 1976 - November 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Stations: Landover, L'Enfant Plaza, August 1977 - October 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Stations: McPherson Square, Medical Center, March 1978 - October 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Station: Metro Center 1, September 1975 - July 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Station: Metro Center 2, July 1987 - July 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Stations: Grosvenor, Huntington, October 1983 - April 2004; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Stations: Braddock Road, Brookland, Branch Ave, February 1978 - August 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Stations: Capitol Heights, Capitol South, Cheverly, Clarendon, March 1979 - March 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Stations: Cleveland Park, College Park, Columbia Heights, Congress Heights, Courthouse Square, Crystal City, July 1978 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Stations: Deanwood, Dunn Loring, Dupont Circle, February 1977 - March 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Stations: East Falls Church, Eastern Market, Eisenhower Avenue, March 1978 - May 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Stations: Farragut North, Farragut West, March 1976 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Stations: Federal Center, Federal Triangle, Foggy Bottom, Forest Glen, June 1977 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Stations: Fort Totten, Franconia-Springfield, Friendship Heights, February 1978 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Security and TPAs 1, January 1976 - November 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Staff: Security and TPAs 2, September 1982 - October 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Security and TPAs 3, May 1990 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Staff: Sports, October 1967 - May 1968; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Stations: Advertising, Architectural Renderings, Parking, July 1976 - June 1982; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Tres, Women, March 1982 - September 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Stations: Addison Road, Anacostia, April 1982 - May 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Stations: Archives 1, April 1983 - July 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Arlington Cemetery, March 1977 - September 1997; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Ballston, Benning Road, November 1979 - September 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Cities: San Francisco [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Cities: San Francisco [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Chicago, Cleveland, Denver, Fairfax, Fort Worth, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Cities: L.A., Newark, Philadelphia, Prince George's, Quincy, Rosslyn, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Aerials, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Cities, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Cities: A-B, Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Stations [1 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Stations [2 of 2], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - D.C. Aerials [1 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Aerials [2 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Aerials [3 of 3], Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Staff: Rail 3 (General), May 1987 - June 1991; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Staff: Rail - Park, April 1992 - April 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Quality Assurance, Stock Clerk, Start-up, December 1985 - April 1994; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Staff: Rail - Maintenance Support, April 1990 - April 1992; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Rail Roadeo, May 1995 - May 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Rail - Managers, Supervisors, Support Services, February 1976 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Rail - System Maintenance 1, July 1979 - December 1985; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Staff: Rail - System Maintenance 2, December 1985 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Rail - Terminal Operations, Training, December 1985 - January 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Staff: Rail - Track Structures, June 1991 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Staff: Safety, Secretary, February 1983 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Staff: Personnel 1, December 1978 - December 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Staff: Personnel 2, August 1991 - July 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Planning, Programming, December 1978 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Staff: Public, November 1975 - March 2001; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Staff: Risk, Real, October 1981 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Rail Car Maintenance 1, March 1988 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Rail Depot Clerk, March 1988 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Staff: Plant Maintenance 1, October 1991 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Rail 1 (General), September 1980 - February 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Staff: Rail 2 (General), April 1985 - March 1988; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Staff: Deputy GM, Design, EEO, Engineering, June 1969 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Staff: GM, GOVR, Labor, November 1976 - September 2000; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Mark 1, December 1975 - April 1983; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Staff: Mark 2, February 1983 - June 1987; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Staff: Mark 3, August 1987 - October 1990; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Mark 4, October 1990 - September 1996; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Staff: Mark 5, March 1995 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Staff: MISV, Officers, February 1978 - August 1998; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Bus Supervisors, May 1985 - September 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Staff: Bus Training, December 1982 - August 2002; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Staff: Civic Rights, Command Center, Comp, Construction, May 1987 - May 2003; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Staff: Cost Reduction, Counsel, September 1982 - September 1999; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Staff: Facilities Maintenance 1, December 1978 - March 1984; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Staff: Facilities Maintenance 2, March 1984 - January 1989; Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 90, Folder 6)